GTM Platform - AI-Native Go-to-Market
Topcoder Challenge Walkthrough
Architecture: 3 layers
Data - Agent - API + UI
Bottom layer: SQLite data model
5 tables: accounts, contacts, opportunities, signals, icp_profiles
Every table scoped by account_id
Multi-tenancy built in - no schema change needed for a second tenant
Middle layer: ReAct agent loop (Claude Haiku)
THOUGHT / ACTION / ARGS / OBSERVATION - every step logged
Top layer: FastAPI + vanilla JS UI
Real-time agent trace viewer
2 real integrations:
Serper (Google Search) + Gmail OAuth
DATA MODEL
accounts table: domain, name, industry, icp_score
contacts: linked to account by account_id
Every query filtered by account_id - that is multi-tenancy
signals: funding rounds, product launches, hires
Captured from real search results, stored per account
opportunities: links contact to outreach action
stage field supports follow-up sequences in iteration 2
SQLite now, PostgreSQL-compatible
One import change in models.py to scale - nothing else changes
LIVE PROSPECT LOOP
Server running at localhost:8000
System already has 2 seeded accounts:
Rippling (ICP 0.92) and Linear (ICP 0.87)
Running a fresh prospect on stripe.com
Email field empty = draft only, no send
Agent is running...
Step 1: search_news - real Serper API call hitting Google
Step 2: search_contacts - LinkedIn profiles via Serper
Real results, not mocked
Step 3: score_icp - Claude reasons about ICP fit
Score computed from keywords, titles, industries in reasoning text
Step 4: save_contact - best contact written to SQLite
Step 5: draft_email - personalized using the actual signal found
Step 6: ANSWER - agent summarizes the full run
All steps complete
Metric cards: ICP score, contacts found, signals captured, agent steps
Agent trace below - every reasoning step visible
AGENT TRACES
Purple = THOUGHT (agent reasoning)
Blue = TOOL_CALL (action + args)
Green = OBSERVATION (real API response)
The agent thought, called search_news with company name,
got back real Serper results, then decided next step
Traces also saved as JSON to /traces/
Primary evidence for Category 1: Real AI/Agent Integration
Each entry: type, timestamp, content
TOOL_CALL has tool name + args
OBSERVATION has what came back from the real API
Nothing mocked or hardcoded
Every agent step used real Claude Haiku
Every search result came from real Serper API
INTEGRATIONS
backbone/integrations.py - all external API calls
search_news: one Serper call
Query: " news funding product launch 2025 2026"
Returns: title, link, snippet
search_contacts: Serper querying LinkedIn
"site:linkedin.com/in  CEO CTO VP Head Director"
send_email: Gmail OAuth2
Loads token, builds MIMEText, posts to Gmail API
Returns message_id on success
Adding a 3rd integration (HubSpot, Slack, Salesforce):
- 1 function in integrations.py
- 1 line in agent system prompt
- 1 elif in _call_tool()
Agent code does not change.
TESTS
26 integration tests, all passing
Tests cover: data model CRUD, multi-tenancy isolation,
agent parsing, ICP scoring, tool dispatch, full loop, API endpoints
WHAT IS NOT BUILT (iteration 1)
Multi-step sequences, reply tracking, CRM pipeline view, Slack notifications
Data model already supports iteration 2:
opportunities.stage field, signals table, extensible schema
Deliberate decisions:
- SQLite over PostgreSQL (runs on reviewer's machine, one command)
- Haiku over GPT-4 (10x cheaper, full run < $0.01)
- Vanilla JS over React (no build step, loads instantly)
github.com/0x-auth/gtm-platform
26 tests passing. 4 real agent traces. 2 live integrations.